export const QuizData = [
  {
    question:
      "Which of the following is a part of the Central Processing Unit?",
    options: ["Printer", "Keyboard", "Mouse", "ALU"],
    answer: 4,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Microprocessors as switching devices are for which generation computers",
    options: [
      "First Generation",
      "Second Generation",
      "Third Generation",
      "Forth Generation",
    ],
    answer: 4,
  },
  {
    question: "Who invented the high level language 'C' ?",
    options: [
      "Dennis M. Ritchie",
      "Niklaus Writh",
      "Seymour Papert",
      "Donald Kunth",
    ],
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "The brain of any computer system is",
    options: ["ALU", "Memory", "CPU", "Control unit"],
    answer: 3,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which of the following computer language is used for artificial intelligence?",
    options: ["FORTRAN", "PROLOG", "C", "COBOL"],
    answer: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Which language runs in web browsers",
    options: ["Java", "C", "Python", "JavaScript"],
    answer: 4,
  },
  {
    question: "is an OOP principle",
    options: [
      "Structured programming",
      "Procedural programming",
      "Inheritance",
      "Linking",
    ],
    answer: 3,
  },
  {
    question: "Computer Monitor is also known as",
    options: ["DVU", "UVD", "CCTV", "VDU"],
    answer: 4,
  },
  {
    question: "Arrange in ascending order the units of memory TB, KB, GB, MB",
    options: ["TB>GB>MB>KB", "TB>MB>GB>KB", "MB>GB>TB>KB", "GB>MB>KB>TB"],
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Which one of these stores more data than a DVD?",
    options: ["CD Rom", "Floppy", "Blue Ray Disk", "Red Ray Disk"],
    answer: 3,
  },
  // {
  //   question: "Eight Bits make up a",
  //   options: ["byte", "megabyte", "kilobyte", "none"],
  //   answer: 1,
  // },
  // {
  //   question: "Which one of these is also known as read/write memory?",
  //   options: ["ROM", "RAM", "DVD", "Hard Disk"],
  //   answer: 2,
  // },
  // {
  //   question: "The printed output from a computer is called",
  //   options: ["Copy", "Soft Copy", "Hard Copy", "Paper"],
  //   answer: 3,
  // },
  // {
  //   question: "MS-Word is an example of",
  //   options: [
  //     "An operating system",
  //     ".A processing device",
  //     "Application software",
  //     "An input device",
  //   ],
  //   answer: 3,
  // },
  // {
  //   question: "Who is the father of Computer?",
  //   options: [
  //     "Allen Turing",
  //     "Charles Babbage",
  //     "Simur Cray",
  //     "Augusta Adaming",
  //   ],
  //   answer: 2,
  // },
  // {
  //   question: "PARAM is an example of:",
  //   options: ["Super Computer", "PC", "Laptop", "PDA"],
  //   answer: 1,
  // },
  // {
  //   question: "You organize files by storing them in",
  //   options: ["archives", "folders", "indexes", "lists"],
  //   answer: 2,
  // },
  // {
  //   question: "Which device is required for the Internet connection?",
  //   options: ["Joystick", "Modem", "CD Drive", "NIC Card"],
  //   answer: 2,
  // },
  // {
  //   question: "ALU  is",
  //   options: [
  //     "Arithmetic Logic Unit",
  //     "Array Logic Unit",
  //     "Application Logic Unit",
  //     "None of above",
  //   ],
  //   answer: 1,
  // },
  // {
  //   question: "The capacity of 3.5 inch floppy disk is",
  //   options: ["1.40 MB", "1.44 GB", "1.40 GB", "1.44 MB"],
  //   answer: 4,
  // },
];
